So, I don't know, for me, the programming
is dead, well, long live programming.
Because so many times we think we've
killed programming, in the end, it's
always
I don't know how it does it, but it
survives.
I'm Miguel Ángel Durán, with over 15 years
of experience developing
software, you can find me on all social
media platforms that allow me, like
Midudev, where I have a community of over
3 million wonderful people who are here
among them and I thank them infinitely for
being part of this community.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you from the bottom of my heart,
really.
I appreciate it a lot.
I have to warn, especially that guy who's
looking for me on Instagram right now
saying, let's see, let's see if they come
out in bikinis.
Well, I have some good news and some bad
news.
If you search for midudev, I do come out
in a bikini, but it's this one.
Okay? It's my cousin Indio, who is a
model, of swimwear, and he
yes, if you search for midudev, you'll
find him there, this isn't me,
okay? Or how much this guy has changed,
huh?
Since he started running, oh my god, no,
it's not me.
On Instagram I'm Midu.
this one, this one is me.
I'm saying this so you're happy when you
go to midudev and don't get any surprises.
I'm also famous because now I have a fight
with the football league in Spain
I've been in the newspaper because I found
that the league blocks us now
when there's football, so we block a lot
of websites to try to combat piracy.
And this is my archenemy, who is the
president of the league,
his name is Javier Tebas, okay?
And Javier Tebas says that they are
websites of 4 geeks, the funny one, right?
Well, what can we do?
Also in Chile, here nearby, I'm in the
newspapers for things like this,
they split your salary a Spanish
influencer destroys a job offer in Chile
for
false part-time hours.
And this photo, huh?
That This is real, this photo, I don't
know, I mean, it looks like
I'm doing something like I'm at the
doctor's, well, anyway, I'm not
going to explain this, it looks like I'm
doing.
I prefer to think it's a little more like
this.
Okay? To destroy the job offers that are
bad.
Well, this is me, this is me, but I'm here
to talk to you about a lot of things,